ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS, EVENTS, AND GROUPS ARE FICTITIOUS
جميع الشخصيات والأماكن والمنظمات والأحداث والمجموعات خيالية
CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS WERE FILMED IN SAFE CONDITIONS
تم تصوير الممثلين الأطفال والحيوانات في ظروف آمنة
Dong-ju!
دونغ جو!
This is great.
هذا عظيم.
You bastard!
أيها الوغد!
I told you.
أخبرتك.
I used to be a champion.
لقد كنت بطلاً.
I was right.
لقد كنت على حق.
This bastard can't see anything.
هذا الوغد لا يستطيع رؤية أي شيء.
Didn't I tell you to watch your blood pressure?
ألم أخبرك أن تراقب ضغط دمك؟
Serves you right for not taking your coach's words seriously.
أنت على حق لأنك لم تأخذ كلام مدربك على محمل الجد.
How do you expect to fight me in that state?
كيف تتوقع أن تقاتلني في هذه الحالة؟
I can beat you no problem even with my eyes closed.
أستطيع أن أهزمك دون مشكلة حتى مع عيني مغلقة.
VICTORY GYM
صالة فيكتوري الرياضية
Take it easy!
خذها ببساطة!
I'm bouncing around, damn it.
أنا أقفز هنا وهناك، اللعنة.
Why are you walking?
لماذا تمشي؟
Go faster! Do you want me to bleed out to death?
أسرع! هل تريدني أن أنزف حتى الموت؟
It was a rubber bullet, so you'll be okay, sir.
لقد كانت رصاصة مطاطية، لذلك ستكون بخير، سيدي.
Rubber, my ass.
مطاط مؤخرتي.
Move carefully!
تحرك بحذر!
Open the ambulance doors!
افتحوا أبواب سيارة الإسعاف!
INSUNG METROPOLITAN POLICE AGENCY
وكالة شرطة العاصمة إنسونغ
Hey, be careful!
مهلا، كن حذرا!
Watch it, you punks!
شاهدوا ذلك أيها الأوغاد!
Didn't I tell you to call a helicopter?
ألم أخبرك باستدعاء طائرة هليكوبتر؟
Yoon Dong-ju.
يون دونغ جو.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
What happened to you?
ما حدث لك؟
What's going on--
ماذا يحدث هنا--
Yoon Dong-ju, what's wrong with you?
يون دونغ جو، ما الذي حدث لك؟
-Dong-ju! -Let go, bastard!
-دونغ جو! -اتركه أيها الوغد!
Hey, get a hold of yourself. Yoon Dong-ju!
هيا، تمالك نفسك. يون دونغ جو!
Come on, snap out of it! It's me!
هيا، استيقظ! هذا أنا!
Look at me. Get it together, Yoon Dong-ju.
انظر إليّ. تماسك يا يون دونغ جو.
Yoon Dong-ju.
يون دونغ جو.
Jong-hyeon.
جونغ هيون.
Wait, you…
انتظر انت…
I…
أنا…
I can't see anything.
لا أستطيع رؤية أي شيء.
Yoon Dong-ju!
يون دونغ جو!
Dong-ju.
دونغ جو.
Dung-ju!
دونج جو!
Yoon Dong-ju!
يون دونغ جو!
Jong-hyeon!
جونغ هيون!
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Min Ju-yeong slipped out already.
لقد انزلقت مين جو يونغ بالفعل.
Where did the bastard run off to? Did you run the plates?
إلى أين هرب ذلك الوغد؟ هل نظفتَ الأطباق؟
They won't let us access the CCTVs in the agency.
لن يسمحوا لنا بالوصول إلى كاميرات المراقبة الموجودة في الوكالة.
The agency is an absolute mess.
الوكالة عبارة عن فوضى مطلقة.
Everyone's clueless and busy tiptoeing around the commissioner.
الجميع في حيرة من أمرهم ومنشغلون بالتسلل حول المفوض.
And the commissioner was harboring a criminal!
والمفوض كان يؤوي مجرمًا!
Shouldn't they investigate the commissioner first?
ألا ينبغي عليهم التحقيق مع المفوض أولاً؟
And who's going to do that?
ومن سيفعل ذلك؟
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
You guys pull footage from nearby CCTVs
لقد قمتم بسحب لقطات من كاميرات المراقبة القريبة
and trace the vehicle's movements.
وتتبع تحركات المركبة.
We'll go roughen up the commissioner.
سنذهب لمعاملة المفوض بقسوة.
-Let's go. -Yes, sir.
-دعنا نذهب. -نعم سيدي.
SERGEANT KIM JONG-HYEON
الرقيب كيم جونغ هيون
Hey, Sergeant Kim. Did you find Dong-ju?
أهلاً، الرقيب كيم. هل وجدتَ دونغ جو؟
Got it. Take him there for now.
فهمت. خذه إلى هناك الآن.
What's wrong with Dung-ju?
ما هو الخطأ مع دونج جو؟
He's not well.
إنه ليس بخير.
-What? -Captain!
-ماذا؟ -كابتن!
I'll tell you later.
سأخبرك لاحقا.
Senior Officer Ji!
الضابط الكبير جي!
Good work.
عمل جيد.
Let's go see the commissioner. Come on.
لنذهب لرؤية المفوض. هيا.
Have you seen Dong-ju or Jong-hyeon?
هل رأيت دونغ جو أو جونغ هيون؟
Oh, right. They're--
أوه، صحيح. إنهم--
They're tracking down Min Ju-yeong
إنهم يتعقبون مين جو يونغ
-and went ahead. -Right, they did.
-ومضي قدمًا. -حسنًا، لقد فعلوا ذلك.
-Come on. Let's go. -They were super quick.
-هيا بنا. -لقد كانوا سريعين جدًا.
I'm dying here.
انا اموت هنا.
Come on. Hurry up.
هيا، أسرع.
Oh, my poor butt!
أوه، مؤخرتي المسكينة!
It hurts so much. Hurry it up already.
إنه يؤلمني كثيرًا. أسرعي.
Stop!
قف!
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
-What the heck? -What are you doing?
-ماذا بحق الجحيم؟ -ماذا تفعل؟
Commissioner, where's Min Ju-yeong? Tell us where he went.
أيها المفوض، أين مين جو يونغ؟ أخبرنا أين ذهب.
You know where he is, don't you?
أنت تعرف أين هو، أليس كذلك؟
-What do you think you're-- -Stand back!
- ماذا تعتقد أنك-- - ابتعد!
Sir, we have a shitstorm at our hands. Are you not going to do anything?
سيدي، أمامنا كارثة. ألا تنوي فعل شيء؟
You're the damn police commissioner!
أنت مفوض الشرطة اللعين!
What? "Damn police commissioner"?
ماذا؟ "يا مفوض الشرطة اللعين"؟
You spineless weasel.
أيها الوغد الضعيف.
You took the role, but you've been completely useless!
لقد توليت الدور، ولكنك كنت عديم الفائدة تمامًا!
"Spineless weasel"?
"ابن عرس ضعيف الشخصية"؟
-You heard me! -You bastard!
-لقد سمعتني! -يا لك من وغد!
You and your team won't get away with this.
أنت وفريقك لن تفلتوا من هذا.
What kind of officer shoots a commissioner in the ass?
أي نوع من الضباط يطلق النار على مفوض في المؤخرة؟
Where's Ji Han-na?
أين جي هان نا؟
Hey, Riot Police. Find her. Where is she?
يا شرطة مكافحة الشغب، اعثروا عليها. أين هي؟
-Move! -Where's Ji Han-na?
-تحرك! -أين جي هان نا؟
-Let's go. -Okay.
-دعنا نذهب. -حسنًا.
Come on. Get moving.
هيا، تحرك.
-Aren't you ashamed? Aren't you officers? -Please leave.
-ألا تخجلون؟ ألستم أيها الضباط؟ -انصرفوا من فضلكم.
What are you all doing? Get rid of him!
ماذا تفعلون جميعًا؟ تخلصوا منه!
-Block him. -You should be ashamed!
-احظره. -يجب أن تخجل!
POLICE
شرطة
It's a damn disgrace
إنه عار لعنة
to be part of the Korean police!
أن أكون جزءًا من الشرطة الكورية!
Where are we going?
إلى أين نحن ذاهبون؟
Where's Min Ju-yeong?
أين مين جو يونغ؟
Min Ju-yeong isn't the issue right now.
مين جو يونغ ليست هي القضية الآن.
Just focus on yourself.
فقط ركز على نفسك .
INSUNG SEONGSIM HOSPITAL
مستشفى إنسونغ سونغسيم
Why are we here?
لماذا نحن هنا؟
Go get an in-depth examination.
اذهب للحصول على فحص متعمق.
The doctor who helped you before is waiting inside.
الطبيب الذي ساعدك سابقًا ينتظرك بالداخل.
She knows about your situation, so she'll handle things discreetly.
إنها تعرف وضعك، لذلك ستتعامل مع الأمور بتكتم.
I'll explain things to Han-na.
سأشرح الأمور لهانا.
Forget it. I don't need to get examined.
انسي الأمر. لا أحتاج إلى فحص.
Are you afraid?
هل انت خائف؟
Why would I be afraid?
لماذا اكون خائفة؟
You know better than anyone how dangerous it is to be punch-drunk.
أنت تعرف أكثر من أي شخص آخر مدى خطورة أن تكون في حالة سُكر.
Want me to hold your hand?
هل تريدني أن أمسك يدك؟
I'm not a kid.
أنا لست طفلا.
Jong-hyeon.
جونغ هيون.
Mr. Yoon Dong-ju.
السيد يون دونغ جو.
She's calling you.
إنها تتصل بك.
Please come in.
من فضلك ادخل.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
For looking out for me.
لاهتمامك بي.
You must be really unwell. Go inside.
لا بد أنك مريض جدًا. ادخل.
Don't smile. I don't want to grow attached to you.
لا تبتسم. لا أريد أن أتعلق بك.
JONG-HYEON
جونغ هيون
The person you are calling cannot be reached.
لا يمكن الوصول إلى الشخص الذي تتصل به .
You will be directed to voicemail.
سيتم توجيهك إلى البريد الصوتي.
At around 2:20 a.m. today,
حوالي الساعة 2:20 صباحًا اليوم،
gunshots were fired at the Insung Metropolitan Police Agency.
تم إطلاق أعيرة نارية على وكالة شرطة مدينة إينسونغ.
According to reports, several suspects who had fled
وبحسب التقارير فإن عددا من المشتبه بهم الذين فروا
during a recent crackdown on illegal weapons and drug cartels
خلال حملة القمع الأخيرة على الأسلحة غير القانونية وعصابات المخدرات
infiltrated the agency
تسلل إلى الوكالة
and attempted to assassinate Commissioner Cho Pan-yeol.
وحاول اغتيال المفوض تشو بان يول.
That awful man.
هذا الرجل الرهيب.
Serves him right.
يستحق ذلك.
Why are you out so late these days?
لماذا أنت بالخارج في وقت متأخر هذه الأيام؟
With so many violent people causing trouble,
مع وجود العديد من الأشخاص العنيفين الذين يسببون المشاكل،
I felt my heart drop just from watching that news clip before.
لقد شعرت أن قلبي ينخفض بمجرد مشاهدة مقطع الأخبار هذا من قبل.
Don't do anything dangerous like that again.
لا تفعل أي شيء خطير مثل هذا مرة أخرى.
Take orders from above, but be smart about it.
خذ الأوامر من الأعلى، ولكن كن ذكيا في التعامل معها.
Okay, I'll be careful.
حسنًا، سأكون حذرًا.
Where's Dung-ju?
أين دونج جو؟
Oh, my husband took him to the vet.
أوه، زوجي أخذه إلى الطبيب البيطري.
Is he sick?
هل هو مريض؟
I don't know. They have to run some tests to find out.
لا أعلم. عليهم إجراء بعض الاختبارات لمعرفة ذلك.
He looks strong and healthy,
يبدو قويا وصحيا،
but he worries me sick.
لكن هذا يقلقني كثيرًا.
INSUNG REDEVELOPMENT SHOOTOUT SUSPECT BREAKS INTO POLICE AGENCY…
مشتبه به في إطلاق النار في إعادة التطوير يقتحم وكالة الشرطة...
Jeez, he's snoring like a chain saw.
يا إلهي، إنه يشخر مثل المنشار الكهربائي.
Don't take it out on the pillow.
لا تخرجه على الوسادة.
Man-sik, why do you keep sleeping here instead of in your own home?
مان-سيك، لماذا تستمر في النوم هنا بدلاً من منزلك؟
Going home will just stress me out more.
العودة إلى المنزل سوف تجعلني أكثر توتراً.
INSUNG POLICE COMMISSIONER TARGETED… COMMISSIONER CHO NOW IN EMERGENCY SURGERY
مفوض شرطة إنسونغ مستهدف... المفوض تشو الآن في جراحة الطوارئ
I'm flying out today. We need to talk.
سأسافر اليوم. نحتاج للتحدث.
Dong-ju's okay.
دونغ جو بخير.
Don't worry. I made sure he got examined.
لا تقلق، لقد تأكدت من فحصه.
SERGEANT KIM JONG-HYEON
الرقيب كيم جونغ هيون
Mayor Roh.
عمدة روه.
What did I just tell you?
ماذا قلت لك للتو؟
You said a ship will arrive
لقد قلت أن السفينة سوف تصل
from Japan tomorrow night.
من اليابان غدا في الليل.
Exactly.
بالضبط.
I told you we need to load the goods on board and set sail.
لقد أخبرتك أننا بحاجة إلى تحميل البضائع على متن السفينة والإبحار.
Just let me get on that ship and leave.
فقط دعني أركب تلك السفينة وأغادر.
I'll…
سوف…
I'll do whatever I can
سأفعل كل ما بوسعي
to make that happen.
لتحقيق ذلك.
Your survival depends on my survival.
بقاءك يعتمد على بقائي.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Would you rather we die together…
هل تفضل أن نموت معًا؟
along with your son, your daughter-in-law, and your grandson?
مع ابنك وزوجة ابنك وحفيدك؟
No.
لا.
Look, I'll make it happen.
انظر، سأجعل ذلك يحدث.
You can go now.
يمكنك الذهاب الآن.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
The ship departed Japan.
غادرت السفينة اليابان.
We have to move quickly and secure the Candy for the deal.
علينا التحرك بسرعة وتأمين الحلوى للصفقة.
If the deal falls through again,
إذا فشلت الصفقة مرة أخرى،
the Japanese won't just let it slide.
لن يسمح اليابانيون بهذا الأمر.
We'll have to retrieve the goods that Mr. Baek took then.
سيتعين علينا استعادة البضائع التي أخذها السيد بايك إذن.
Even the Buk-dong and Black Dragon guys?
حتى رجال بوك دونج والتنين الأسود؟
They won't take Mr. Min's goods.
لن يأخذوا بضائع السيد مين.
Those dumb cowards.
هؤلاء الجبناء الاغبياء.
I think Mr. Min is looking for us.
أعتقد أن السيد مين يبحث عنا.
What should we do?
ماذا يجب علينا أن نفعل؟
Who the hell is it?
من هو هذا الجحيم؟
What is this idiot saying?
ماذا يقول هذا الأحمق؟
"Friend"?
"صديق"؟
I may not be fluent in English, but I do know that word.
قد لا أكون متمكنًا من اللغة الإنجليزية، ولكنني أعرف هذه الكلمة.
We're not friends.
نحن لسنا أصدقاء.
Gosh, Mr. Min.
يا إلهي، السيد مين.
I thought you were dead, but you're alive and well.
اعتقدت أنك ميت، ولكنك على قيد الحياة وبصحة جيدة.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Are you disappointed?
هل أنت محبط؟
Of course not. You've got it all wrong.
بالطبع لا، لقد فهمت الأمر بشكل خاطئ.
Then what's with the look on your face?
إذن ما الأمر مع المظهر الذي على وجهك؟
It's as if you were caught stealing.
كأنك تم القبض عليك متلبسا بالسرقة.
Stealing? What do you mean?
سرقة؟ ماذا تقصد؟
I think those belong to me.
أعتقد أن هذه ملكي.
How are those all yours?
كيف هي كل تلك الأشياء لك؟
What about the price for my men's blood?
ماذا عن ثمن دماء رجالي؟
Now that Drugmon and the Black Cat bastard are dead,
الآن بعد أن مات دروج مون والقط الأسود الوغد،
why don't we survivors split it?
لماذا لا نقوم نحن الناجين بتقسيمها؟
Fairly.
إلى حد ما.
What do you say?
ماذا تقول؟
Sounds good.
ًيبدو جيدا.
Let's do that.
دعونا نفعل ذلك.
We'll play it fair…
سوف نلعبها بشكل عادل...
and let the survivor take it all.
ودع الناجي يأخذ كل شيء.
Fuck you.
اذهب للجحيم.
Min Ju-yeong, you son of a bitch!
مين جو يونغ، يا ابن العاهرة!
Yes, Captain.
نعم يا كابتن.
I just got word.
لقد حصلت للتو على الكلمة.
Yes.
نعم.
I'll go straight to the scene.
سأذهب مباشرة إلى مكان الحادث.
Dong-ju?
دونغ جو؟
He got examined until dawn, so he should be sleeping…
لقد تم فحصه حتى الفجر، لذا يجب أن يكون نائماً...
Hey, did you miss me?
مهلا، هل افتقدتني؟
You grew so much.
لقد كبرت كثيرا.
You little cutie.
يا صغيرتي اللطيفة.
What are you doing here? You didn't even check my text.
ماذا تفعل هنا؟ لم تتحقق حتى من رسالتي.
Sorry.
آسف.
My phone got busted.
لقد تم اختراق هاتفي.
Are you coming back from tracking Min Ju-yeong?
هل ستعود من تعقب مين جو يونغ؟
I missed you.
أفتقدك.
Goodness, how sweet.
يا إلهي، كم هو جميل.
You're back.
لقد عدت.
You look great together. What a good-looking pair.
تبدوان رائعين معًا. يا لهما من ثنائي رائع.
Thank you, ma'am.
شكرا لك سيدتي.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
DUNG-JU
دونج جو
Hey, there he is.
مهلا، هو هناك.
-Hey. -Dung-ju, come over here.
-مرحبًا. -دونج-جو، تعال إلى هنا.
Hey.
يا.
You should've stayed in the hospital. Why did you come here?
كان يجب عليك البقاء في المستشفى. لماذا أتيت إلى هنا؟
I can work and get treatment at the same time.
أستطيع العمل والحصول على العلاج في نفس الوقت.
If you stop me, I won't get treatment.
إذا أوقفتني، فلن أحصل على العلاج.
If anything happens to me, it'll be your fault.
إذا حدث لي أي شيء، فسيكون ذلك خطؤك.
What kind of crap is that?
ما هذا النوع من الهراء؟
You're still wanted!
لا زال مطلوبا منك!
Han-na, the crime scene is over there.
هانا، مسرح الجريمة موجود هناك.
What if other cops see you?
ماذا لو رأى رجال الشرطة الآخرين لك؟
I've already confirmed that only the RIU and the forensics team are here.
لقد تأكدت بالفعل من أن فريق RIU وفريق الطب الشرعي فقط هم المتواجدون هنا.
Besides, nobody will notice me in this situation.
وبالإضافة إلى ذلك، لن يلاحظني أحد في هذا الوضع.
You and that smart mouth of yours.
أنت وهذا فمك الذكي.
Why won't you listen to me?
لماذا لا تستمع لي؟
Hey, Dong-ju.
مهلا، دونغ جو.
-Hey. -Are you okay? What did the doctor say?
-مرحبًا. -هل أنتِ بخير؟ ماذا قال الطبيب؟
The doctor? Why? Is someone sick?
الطبيب؟ لماذا؟ هل هناك مريض؟
Is it Ha-min, Ha-jun, Ha-yul, or Ha-yeong?
هل هو ها مين، ها جون، ها يول، أو ها يونغ؟
What are you talking about?
ماذا تتحدث عنه؟
Dong-ju slept with me.
لقد نام دونغ جو معي.
In separate rooms.
في غرف منفصلة.
Oh, right. My wife is sick.
أوه، صحيح. زوجتي مريضة.
-How sick is she? -Come on, she wouldn't have noticed.
-ما مدى مرضها؟ -هيا، لن تلاحظ ذلك.
Yeah, it was. Come on, Jae-hong.
نعم، كان كذلك. هيا يا جاي هونغ.
I smoothly changed the subject to my wife.
لقد غيرت الموضوع بسلاسة إلى زوجتي.
Hey, you guys go on ahead.
مهلا، يا رفاق، اذهبوا إلى الأمام.
-Okay. -We'll start the car.
-حسنًا. -سنبدأ تشغيل السيارة.
EVIDENCE: SUNFLOWER SEED SHELLS
الدليل: قشور بذور عباد الشمس
Where's Baek Seok-chun?
أين بايك سوك تشون؟
There's no body, so he probably escaped.
لا يوجد جثة، لذا فمن المحتمل أنه هرب.
The locals heard gunshots
سمع السكان المحليون طلقات نارية
and saw some Russians and Min Ju-yeong.
ورأيت بعض الروس ومين جو يونغ.
But we don't know where they disappeared to.
ولكننا لا نعلم أين اختفوا.
We checked all the footage starting from the agency,
لقد قمنا بفحص جميع اللقطات بدءًا من الوكالة،
but we have no idea how they got here.
ولكن ليس لدينا أي فكرة عن كيفية وصولهم إلى هنا.
Wait. That's strange.
انتظر. هذا غريب.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
Well, to get anywhere else from here,
حسنًا، للوصول إلى أي مكان آخر من هنا،
he would've had to get past seven checkpoints set up along the way.
كان عليه أن يتجاوز سبع نقاط تفتيش أقيمت على طول الطريق.
So how did he manage to avoid them all?
فكيف تمكن من تجنبهم جميعا؟
You're right.
أنت على حق.
It means someone inside the force
يعني شخص داخل القوة
is continuing to help Min Ju-yeong.
يستمر في مساعدة مين جو يونغ.
So there's another rat in addition to your rookie.
إذن هناك فأر آخر بالإضافة إلى مبتدئك.
Yes. But I don't think it was our rookie.
نعم، ولكن لا أعتقد أنه كان لاعبنا المبتدئ.
This is an agency-issued .38 caliber handgun.
هذا مسدس عيار 38 تم إصداره من قبل وكالة.
The grip here matches his wound exactly.
القبضة هنا تتطابق مع جرحه تمامًا.
Wait. Are you saying the killer is a cop?
انتظر. هل تقول أن القاتل شرطي؟
It looks like it.
يبدو الأمر كذلك.
We looked into our rookie,
لقد نظرنا إلى مبتدئنا،
but nothing connected him to Min Ju-yeong.
ولكن لا شيء يربطه بمين جو يونغ.
If the rat is a cop,
إذا كان الفأر شرطيًا،
maybe they silenced your rookie after getting caught.
ربما قاموا بإسكات مبتدئك بعد القبض عليه.
I'm ashamed to say this, but one thing's clear.
أشعر بالخجل من قول هذا، ولكن هناك شيء واحد واضح.
That rat is on our team.
هذا الفأر في فريقنا.
If Min Ju-yeong escaped while evading the patrols and checkpoints,
إذا هربت مين جو يونغ أثناء التهرب من الدوريات ونقاط التفتيش،
he probably headed west.
ربما كان متجها نحو الغرب.
Assuming he hasn't left Insung City,
على افتراض أنه لم يغادر مدينة إنسونغ،
the likely places where he could be hiding
الأماكن المحتملة التي من الممكن أن يختبئ فيها
can be narrowed down to Seo-gu, Daejeong-gu, and Hoeun-gu.
يمكن تضييق نطاقها إلى Seo-gu وDaejeong-gu وHoeun-gu.
This is the list of people who attended
هذه هي قائمة الأشخاص الذين حضروا
the special joint task force launch ceremony.
حفل إطلاق قوة المهام المشتركة الخاصة .
The majority of the attendees
أغلبية الحضور
will be connected to Min Ju-yeong in some shape or form.
سيتم ربطها بـ Min Ju-yeong في شكل أو آخر.
Some on this list must own buildings
يجب أن يمتلك بعض الأشخاص في هذه القائمة مباني
in Seo-gu, Daejeong-gu, and Hoeun-gu.
في سيو غو، ودايجيونغ غو، وهويون غو.
If we focus our efforts on that, we'll catch Min Ju-yeong.
إذا ركزنا جهودنا على ذلك، فسوف نتمكن من القبض على مين جو يونغ.
Everyone who's anyone in Insung is on this list.
كل شخص مهم في Insung موجود في هذه القائمة.
It might take some time,
قد يستغرق الأمر بعض الوقت،
but let's see who owns buildings in those areas
ولكن دعونا نرى من يملك المباني في تلك المناطق
and look for Min Ju-yeong's hideout.
وابحث عن مخبأ مين جو يونغ.
Hey, someone's here.
مرحبًا، هناك شخص هنا.
Now who's this?
الآن من هذا؟
I want people to leave, not show up.
أريد من الناس أن يغادروا، وليس أن يظهروا.
Goodness, everyone's all here.
يا إلهي، الجميع هنا.
Even our fugitive.
حتى الهارب لدينا.
Not you.
ليس انت.
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
I thought you might want an update on the commissioner.
اعتقدت أنك قد ترغب في الحصول على تحديث بشأن المفوض.
Why would I want an update
لماذا أريد التحديث
unless he kicked the bucket during surgery?
إلا إذا توفي أثناء إجراء عملية جراحية؟
He's fine.
إنه بخير.
By the way, how did you manage to shoot him
بالمناسبة كيف تمكنت من إطلاق النار عليه؟
without damaging a single nerve?
دون الإضرار بأي عصب واحد؟
Even the doctors were amazed.
حتى الأطباء كانوا مندهشين.
You were a national athlete for a reason.
لقد كنت رياضيًا وطنيًا لسبب ما.
Senior Office Ji is the best at shooting…
كبير موظفي جي هو الأفضل في التصويب…
Sorry, sir.
عذرا سيدي.
My apologies.
اعتذاري.
You should've aimed for his butthole while you were at it.
كان ينبغي عليك أن تستهدف فتحة الشرج الخاصة به أثناء قيامك بذلك.
I think the commissioner has his own struggles.
أعتقد أن المفوض لديه صراعاته الخاصة.
He said to cancel the APB on Yoon Dong-ju.
وقال لإلغاء APB على Yoon Dong-ju.
Why the sudden change of heart?
لماذا هذا التغير المفاجئ في القلب؟
It means he won't get involved,
وهذا يعني أنه لن يتدخل،
but he'll turn a blind eye to your efforts in catching Min Ju-yeong.
لكنّه سيتجاهل جهودك في القبض على مين جو يونغ.
But if things go wrong, we'll end up taking the fall.
لكن إذا سارت الأمور بشكل خاطئ، فسوف ننتهي بتحمل المسؤولية.
What the heck is he up to? It's like he's on the fence.
ماذا يفعل بحق الجحيم؟ يبدو وكأنه على الحياد.
I don't think Min Ju-yeong and the commissioner
لا أعتقد أن مين جو يونغ والمفوض
are directly connected.
متصلين بشكل مباشر.
But he can't step up because of the mayor and other influential people involved.
ولكنه لا يستطيع أن يتولى المهمة بسبب رئيس البلدية وبعض الأشخاص المؤثرين الآخرين المتورطين.
So I tried to feel him out.
لذلك حاولت أن أشعر به.
I can't get involved.
لا أستطيع التدخل.
What if something goes wrong?
ماذا لو حدث خطأ ما؟
Who knows what that bastard has in his arsenal?
من يعلم ماذا يملك هذا الوغد في ترسانته؟
Don't forget
لا تنسى
that money…
تلك الأموال…
isn't the only thing in my arsenal.
ليس هذا هو الشيء الوحيد في ترسانتي.
Money isn't the only thing in his arsenal, huh?
المال ليس الشيء الوحيد في ترسانته، أليس كذلك؟
If it's not money,
إذا لم يكن المال،
then why is everyone groveling to Min Ju-yeong?
إذن لماذا يزحف الجميع إلى مين جو يونغ؟
Min Ju-yeong is the type to find someone's weakness
مين جو يونغ هو من النوع الذي يجد نقاط ضعف شخص ما
and control them.
والسيطرة عليهم.
He must have something big enough to keep them powerless for so long.
لا بد أن يكون لديه شيء كبير بما يكفي لإبقائهم عاجزين لفترة طويلة.
The people on this list
الأشخاص الموجودين في هذه القائمة
mostly come from families that made their fortunes through trade.
معظمهم يأتون من عائلات جمعت ثرواتها من خلال التجارة.
Some still run their own companies
بعضهم لا يزالون يديرون شركاتهم الخاصة
including the father of the departmental chief prosecutor.
بما في ذلك والد المدعي العام الإقليمي.
This is the list of companies.
وهذه قائمة الشركات.
Every company on this list
كل شركة في هذه القائمة
took off once Min Ju-yeong started managing them.
انطلقت عندما بدأ مين جو يونج في إدارتها.
If you find out what he did back then,
إذا اكتشفت ما فعله في ذلك الوقت،
you'll find out the weaknesses he has on them.
ستكتشف نقاط الضعف التي لديه عليهم.
Where did you get this from anyway?
من أين حصلت على هذا على أي حال؟
Jeez, you think I went on that business trip for fun?
يا إلهي، هل تعتقد أنني ذهبت في رحلة العمل تلك من أجل المتعة؟
Believe it or not, I worked in intelligence.
صدق أو لا تصدق، لقد عملت في الاستخبارات.
Min Ju-yeong was initially assigned to the Information Management Division.
تم تعيين مين جو يونغ في البداية في قسم إدارة المعلومات.
He was in charge of managing the integrated database.
وكان مسؤولاً عن إدارة قاعدة البيانات المتكاملة.
Integrated database?
قاعدة بيانات متكاملة؟
The Korea Customs Service was transitioning to an electronic system.
كانت دائرة الجمارك الكورية في طور التحول إلى النظام الإلكتروني.
His job was to digitize paper records and then destroy the documents.
كانت وظيفته هي رقمنة السجلات الورقية ومن ثم تدمير الوثائق.
Documents, huh?
وثائق، هاه؟
What kind of documents?
ما نوع الوثائق؟
IMPORT TAX INVOICE (CUSTOMS COPY) COMPANY NAME: CHEONGIL SHIPPING
فاتورة ضريبة الاستيراد (نسخة جمركية) اسم الشركة: تشونجيل للشحن
Mr. Lee Jin-su was in charge of Cheongil Shipping.
وكان السيد لي جين سو مسؤولاً عن شركة تشيونجيل للشحن.
Could that be connected as well?
هل يمكن أن يكون ذلك متصلا أيضا؟
Now that I think about it,
الآن بعد أن فكرت في الأمر،
Cheongil Shipping was audited
تم تدقيق شركة تشيونجيل للشحن
for fraudulent tax invoices shortly before its bankruptcy.
بسبب فواتير ضريبية احتيالية قبل فترة وجيزة من إفلاسها.
Hold on, I just saw it.
انتظر، لقد رأيته للتو.
Right here.
هنا.
It says here an insider tip triggered an investigation.
ويقال هنا أن بلاغًا داخليًا أدى إلى فتح تحقيق.
If the insider had been Min Ju-yeong…
لو كان المطلع هو مين جو يونغ...
He must've found the fraudulent tax invoices
لا بد أنه وجد الفواتير الضريبية المزورة
before the system went digital.
قبل أن يصبح النظام رقميًا.
One of the invoices must've been Cheongil Shipping's.
يبدو أن إحدى الفواتير كانت لشركة Cheongil Shipping.
I see.
أرى.
Now it all makes sense.
الآن أصبح كل شيء منطقيًا.
He hit the jackpot with those documents.
لقد فاز بالجائزة الكبرى مع تلك الوثائق.
He used those documents to blackmail companies for bribes
لقد استخدم تلك الوثائق لابتزاز الشركات مقابل الرشوة
and to build a network.
وبناء شبكة.
With powerful connections backing him,
مع وجود علاقات قوية تدعمه،
he lost his head.
لقد فقد رأسه.
I told you that I don't know!
لقد قلت لك أنني لا أعرف!
Why are you asking me about Oh Dollar's whereabouts?
لماذا تسألني عن مكان وجود أوه دولار؟
He took out Oh Dollar and tricked Leo…
أخرج أوه دولار وخدع ليو...
into wiping out all the other gangs.
في القضاء على جميع العصابات الأخرى.
GWANGHO LOGISTICS 2025 TAX INVOICE
فاتورة ضريبية لشركة غوانغهو لوجيستكس لعام ٢٠٢٥
So Min Ju-yeong slowly took over Insung
سو مين جو يونغ تولى الأمر ببطء
by using the documents he had gathered.
باستخدام الوثائق التي جمعها.
With that kind of leash in his grip,
مع هذا النوع من المقود في قبضته،
he had nothing to fear.
لم يكن لديه ما يخافه.
Get hold of those documents,
احصل على تلك الوثائق
and we can wipe out decades-old scums of Insung
ويمكننا القضاء على حثالات إنسونغ التي مضى عليها عقود من الزمن
in a single blow.
بضربة واحدة.
And where are we to go look for them?
وأين نذهب للبحث عنهم؟
All the containers like the last time?
كل الحاويات مثل المرة السابقة؟
I doubt they're there.
أنا أشك في وجودهم هناك.
He would've hidden such valuable material somewhere more secure.
لقد كان ليخفي مثل هذه المواد القيمة في مكان أكثر أمانًا.
If he had hidden them in containers, we would've found them already.
لو كان قد أخفاهم في حاويات لكنا وجدناهم بالفعل.
We had searched every possible container at the time.
لقد قمنا بتفتيش كل حاوية ممكنة في ذلك الوقت.
Let's just ask one person
دعونا نسأل شخصًا واحدًا فقط
who knows where they are.
من يعرف أين هم؟
Who?
من؟
Min Ju-yeong.
مين جو يونغ.
We'll bait him
سوف نغريه
by letting it slip
عن طريق تركها تنزلق
where we'll strike.
أين سنضرب.
How?
كيف؟
Let's take care of the RIU first.
دعونا نعتني بـRIU أولاً.
The SCIT will handle the north side.
ستتولى SCIT التعامل مع الجانب الشمالي.
The RIU can conduct a thorough search of the south side.
يمكن لـ RIU إجراء بحث شامل في الجانب الجنوبي.
We have to move as discreetly and quietly as possible.
علينا أن نتحرك بحذر وهدوء قدر الإمكان.
INSUNG PAWNSHOP
محل رهن منزلي
If Min Ju-yeong catches on, it'll be all for nothing.
إذا أدركت مين جو يونغ ذلك، فسيكون كل هذا بلا فائدة.
This is our last chance to catch the bastard.
هذه فرصتنا الأخيرة للقبض على هذا الوغد.
Do you understand?
هل تفهم؟
-Yes, sir.
-نعم سيدي.
Please refrain from using your phones.
يرجى الامتناع عن استخدام هواتفكم.
We'll communicate with these. Set it to channel four.
سنتواصل معهم. اضبطه على القناة الرابعة.
Here.
هنا.
Channel four!
القناة الرابعة!
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Let's use the RIU's informant like Dong-ju suggested.
دعونا نستخدم المخبر التابع لـ RIU كما اقترح دونغ جو.
Right now, we can't trust anyone. Not even Dae-yong.
حاليًا، لا يمكننا الوثوق بأحد. ولا حتى داي يونغ.
Okay.
تمام.
-Okay. Let's move. -Yes, sir.
-حسنًا. لنتحرك. -نعم سيدي.
This works, right?
هذا يعمل، أليس كذلك؟
It might look like junk, but the CIA used this in the past.
قد يبدو الأمر وكأنه خردة، لكن وكالة المخابرات المركزية استخدمته في الماضي.
It works perfectly fine across a wide listening range.
إنه يعمل بشكل جيد للغاية عبر نطاق استماع واسع.
And with my skillful touch…
ومع لمستي الماهرة…
Do you actually hear anything?
هل تسمع أي شيء فعليا؟
All he's doing is touching it.
كل ما يفعله هو لمسها.
-Hold it up straight! -Damn it.
-امسكها بشكل مستقيم! -اللعنة.
Do it yourself then.
افعل ذلك بنفسك إذن.
I can't pick up the frequency!
لا أستطيع التقاط التردد!
Put that down.
ضع ذلك.
It's perfectly set up here!
لقد تم إعداده بشكل مثالي هنا!
That punk has no redeeming qualities. He falls short across the board!
هذا الشقي لا يملك أي صفات حميدة. إنه فاشل في كل شيء!
-No sign of him at the intersection. -With my skillful touch…
-لا يوجد أي أثر له عند التقاطع. -مع لمستي الماهرة...
All of you need to get it together.
يجب عليكم جميعًا أن تتعاونوا معًا.
-Stop embarrassing the RIU. -My skillful touch…
-توقف عن إحراج RIU. -لمستي الماهرة...
What are we even doing?
ماذا نفعل حتى؟
-Can we catch Min Ju-yeong this way? -My skillful touch…
-هل يمكننا أن نمسك مين جو يونغ بهذه الطريقة؟ -لمستي الماهرة...
Beats me. Let's just do what they say for now.
لا أفهم. لنفعل ما يقولونه الآن.
It isn't you, Captain, is it?
إنه ليس أنت يا كابتن، أليس كذلك؟
-Jeez, which bastard is it? -With my skillful touch…
-يا إلهي، أي وغد هذا؟ -مع لمستي الماهرة...
I think Go Man-sik is suspecting me.
أعتقد أن جو مان سيك يشك بي.
I need a smoke. I'll be right back.
أحتاج إلى سيجارة. سأعود حالاً.
All that touching and nothing.
كل هذا اللمس ولا شيء.
-Jeez, I'm exhausted. -Okay.
-يا إلهي، أنا مرهق. -حسنًا.
All of my hard work has paid off.
لقد أتى كل عملي الشاق بثماره.
I think one of them is on the phone.
أعتقد أن أحدهم على الهاتف.
Can you hear me?
أيمكنك سماعي؟
I'm not sure, but I think they're looking for you, Mr. Min.
أنا لست متأكدًا، لكن أعتقد أنهم يبحثون عنك، سيد مين.
So we're all on a stakeout.
لذا نحن جميعا في مهمة مراقبة.
I'll help you once you decide on your destination.
سأساعدك عندما تقرر وجهتك.
Also,
أيضًا،
I'll only help once the money's been wired.
سأقوم بالمساعدة فقط بعد تحويل الأموال.
I need your word on that.
أحتاج إلى كلمتك في هذا الشأن.
At least it's not Dae-yong.
على الأقل ليس داي يونغ.
AN DAE-YONG
آن داي يونغ
-You bastard. -What's going on?
-يا لك من وغد. -ماذا يحدث؟
-Don't act like you don't know. -What is it?
-لا تتصرف وكأنك لا تعرف. -ما هو؟
Are you serious, you bastard?
هل أنت جاد أيها الوغد؟
-You asshole! -Out of the way!
-يا أحمق! - ابتعد عن الطريق!
You son of a bitch!
يا ابن العاهرة!
Kick his ass over there!
اركل مؤخرته هناك!
What the hell is wrong with you?
ما الذي حدث لك بحق الجحيم؟
-You know damn well, asshole! -Captain.
-أنت تعرف ذلك جيدًا، أيها الأحمق! -كابتن.
What's your problem?
ما هي مشكلتك؟
-What is this? -Let go of me!
-ما هذا؟ -اتركني!
What are you doing with my phone?
ماذا تفعل بهاتفي؟
Where's your burner phone?
أين هاتفك الحارق؟
What burner phone? What the hell are you talking about?
أي هاتفٍ مُحترق؟ عن ماذا تتحدث؟
Why are you searching the van? Get out.
لماذا تبحث في السيارة؟ اخرج.
We know everything, you little shit.
نحن نعلم كل شيء، أيها الوغد الصغير.
We heard you talking to Min Ju-yeong!
لقد سمعناك تتحدث مع مين جو يونغ!
What the hell are you talking about?
ما الذي تتحدث عنه بحق الجحيم؟
Why would I talk to Min Ju-yeong?
لماذا أريد أن أتحدث مع مين جو يونغ؟
What's the matter with all of you?
ما الأمر معكم جميعا؟
Then what's this?
ثم ما هذا؟
What did Min Ju-yeong tell you?
ماذا قال لك مين جو يونغ؟
-Talk! -He…
-تكلم! -هو...
He didn't say anything.
لم يقل شيئا.
You bastard!
أيها الوغد!
I'm telling the truth.
انا أقول الحقيقة.
He said he got it and would call me back, then hung up.
قال إنه حصل على ذلك وسيتصل بي، ثم أغلق الهاتف.
How long have you been his mole?
منذ متى وأنت الخلد له؟
It hasn't been long. I swear.
لم يمر وقت طويل. أقسم.
What the hell did you tell him?
ماذا قلت له بحق الجحيم؟
All I did was pass on what I knew about the recent investigation.
كل ما فعلته هو أنني نقلت ما أعرفه عن التحقيق الأخير.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Are you okay, sir?
هل انت بخير سيدي؟
It seems that the SCIT requested backup,
يبدو أن اللجنة الخاصة طلبت النسخ الاحتياطي،
so I wanted to see if things were okay.
لذلك أردت أن أرى ما إذا كان كل شيء على ما يرام.
Then…
ثم…
why did you kill the rookie?
لماذا قتلت المبتدئ؟
You damn asshole!
أيها الأحمق اللعين!
Answer me.
يجيبني.
Because he caught me.
لأنه أمسك بي.
Jong-hun.
جونغ هون.
Do you have something to say?
هل لديك شيئا لتقوله؟
Let me explain. Come with me.
دعني أشرح لك. تعال معي.
Just tell me here.
فقط أخبرني هنا.
I said I'd explain. Let's talk over there.
قلتُ إني سأشرح. لنتحدث هناك.
Are you even human, you asshole?
هل أنت إنسان حقًا، أيها الأحمق؟
Do you think Min Ju-yeong has caught on?
هل تعتقد أن مين جو يونغ قد استوعب الأمر؟
Let's squeeze this punk for information.
دعونا نضغط على هذا البانك للحصول على المعلومات.
No, let's wait a bit longer.
لا، دعنا ننتظر لفترة أطول قليلاً.
He'll make a move first.
سوف يقوم بالتحرك أولاً.
How can you be so sure?
كيف يمكنك أن تكون متأكداً إلى هذه الدرجة؟
He may have acted indifferently,
ربما تصرف بلا مبالاة،
but losing all his hidden cash must've come as a shock.
لكن خسارة كل أمواله المخفية لابد وأن كانت بمثابة صدمة.
Once you've been hit, even a fake jab will make you flinch.
بمجرد أن تتلقى ضربة، حتى الضربة المزيفة سوف تجعلك تتراجع.
I know he'll make a move.
أعلم أنه سوف يقوم بالتحرك.
Answer it.
أجب عليه.
This is the last thing you can do…
هذا هو آخر شيء يمكنك فعله…
for Jong-hun.
لجونغ هون.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
RESTRICTED NUMBER
رقم مقيد
Make sure the Gumyeon Intersection is clear.
تأكد من أن تقاطع Gumyeon واضح.
There'll be a truck too.
سيكون هناك شاحنة أيضًا.
I'll check on it and get back to you.
سأتحقق من ذلك وأعود إليك.
What are you all waiting for?
ماذا تنتظرون جميعا؟
Is he really okay? Did he hurt his head that badly?
هل هو بخير حقًا؟ هل كان رأسه مصابًا بهذه الدرجة من الشدة؟
How did he get so smart overnight? It's scaring me.
كيف أصبح ذكيًا جدًا بين عشية وضحاها؟ هذا الأمر يخيفني.
Let's get going.
دعونا ننطلق.
Senior Officer Shin, are you ready?
الضابط الكبير شين، هل أنت مستعد؟
Min Ju-yeong will head toward Gumyeon-dong through the Gumyeon Intersection.
سوف يتجه مين جو يونغ نحو جوميون دونج عبر تقاطع جوميون.
-Keep your eyes open. -Got it.
-ابقي عينيك مفتوحتين. -فهمت.
We'll clear the road for you. Don't worry.
سنُفسِح الطريق لك. لا تقلق.
He's heading toward Insung Middle School.
إنه متجه نحو مدرسة إينسونغ المتوسطة.
Should I dispatch a patrol car?
هل يجب علي إرسال سيارة دورية؟
Yeah.
نعم.
Patrol car number seven, move in.
سيارة دورية رقم سبعة، تحرك.
Patrol, your role is over.
دورية، دورك انتهى.
The vehicle is on the move again.
السيارة تتحرك مرة أخرى.
After taking a left at the Jungang Intersection,
بعد الانعطاف يسارًا عند تقاطع جونغانغ،
they're headed toward Insung Industrial Complex.
إنهم متجهون نحو المجمع الصناعي إينسونغ.
The vehicles are entering the Gumyeon-dong Underpass.
تدخل المركبات إلى نفق جوميون دونج.
Stop, Misha.
توقف يا ميشا.
Why aren't they coming out?
لماذا لا يخرجون؟
Captain, they entered the underpass, but the vehicles haven't exited yet.
يا كابتن، لقد دخلوا إلى النفق، لكن السيارات لم تخرج بعد.
What do you mean they haven't exited?
ماذا تقصد بأنهم لم يخرجوا؟
Jae-hong, we're almost there.
جاي هونغ، لقد وصلنا تقريبًا.
-Is he there? -No.
-هل هو هناك؟ -لا.
The bastard stole a car and escaped through the opposite lane.
قام اللص بسرقة سيارة وهرب عبر المسار المعاكس.
Check the vehicles that exited the underpass!
تحقق من المركبات التي خرجت من النفق!
Can we take a look at the vehicles that exited the underpass?
هل يمكننا إلقاء نظرة على المركبات التي خرجت من النفق؟
They're checking right now.
إنهم يتحققون الآن.
More importantly,
والأهم من ذلك،
-they abandoned the truck. -So what?
-لقد تركوا الشاحنة. -وماذا في ذلك؟
Captain.
قبطان.
What if Min Ju-yeong has no intention of retrieving the documents?
ماذا لو لم يكن لدى مين جو يونغ أي نية لاسترجاع الوثائق؟
Destroy the documents right now.
قم بتدمير المستندات الآن.
Take out every single page…
أخرج كل صفحة على حدة…
and dispose of them all.
والتخلص منهم جميعا.
Where did he keep those documents?
أين احتفظ بتلك الوثائق؟
Once you clear the underpass,
بمجرد عبور النفق السفلي،
you can reach Unseon-dong in Yeonsang-gu
يمكنك الوصول إلى Unseon-dong في Yeonsang-gu
or Geumjeong-dong, Chungmu-dong, and Anseong-dong in Jeong-gu.
أو جيومجيونج دونج، تشونغمو دونج، وأنسيونج دونج في جونغ جو.
Yeonsang-gu?
يون سانج-جو؟
Hold on. The mayor used to be the head of that district.
انتظر. كان رئيس البلدية رئيسًا لتلك المنطقة.
The district head?
رئيس المنطقة؟
I used to live there!
لقد كنت أعيش هناك!
Good work. I'm proud of you.
عمل جيد. أنا فخور بك.
The mayor was born and raised there, so he had it good for a long time.
لقد ولد رئيس البلدية ونشأ هناك، لذا فقد عاش حياة جيدة لفترة طويلة.
He'll need a space large enough to store the documents he wants destroyed.
سوف يحتاج إلى مساحة كبيرة بما يكفي لتخزين المستندات التي يريد تدميرها.
A secure location that can preserve documents for a long time.
مكان آمن يمكنه الحفاظ على المستندات لفترة طويلة.
LIST OF BUILDINGS
قائمة المباني
It's this one.
إنه هذا.
You and I see eye to eye.
أنت وأنا نرى نفس الشيء.
I think so too.
أعتقد ذلك أيضًا.
When the mayor took office as district head,
عندما تولى رئيس البلدية منصبه كرئيس للمنطقة،
the first project he pushed for
أول مشروع دفعه نحوه
was building the Yeonsang-gu Public Library.
كان يقوم ببناء مكتبة يونسانغ-غو العامة.
It has an underground storage facility.
يحتوي على منشأة تخزين تحت الأرض.
-Freeze! -This is the police. Stop immediately!
-تجمّد! -هذه الشرطة. توقّف فورًا!
-Leave it! -Stop the paper shredder!
-اتركها! -أوقف آلة تقطيع الورق!
Don't move!
لا تتحرك!
So these are the corruption-related documents, huh?
إذن هذه هي الوثائق المتعلقة بالفساد، أليس كذلك؟
Fortunately, they didn't destroy much. The majority of them are still here.
لحسن الحظ، لم يُدمِّروا الكثير. لا يزال معظمهم هنا.
COMPANY NAME: TAE CORPORATION
اسم الشركة: شركة تاي
Oh, I found it.
أوه، لقد وجدته.
TAE Corporation.
شركة TAE.
TAE CORPORATION TAX INVOICES
فواتير ضريبة الشركات TAE
Right here.
هنا.
This reeks of corruption.
هذا ينضح بالفساد.
Let's go get him.
دعونا نذهب للحصول عليه.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
-What did Commissioner Cho say? -They didn't allow visitors to see him.
- ماذا قال المفوض تشو؟ - لم يسمحوا للزوار برؤيته.
Damn it, you bastard!
لعنة عليك أيها الوغد!
So you just came back here empty-handed?
فهل عدت للتو إلى هنا خالي الوفاض؟
You've got to be kidding me!
أنت لا بد وأنك تمزح معي!
I'm losing my mind here!
أنا أفقد عقلي هنا!
And that bastard Cho Pan-yeol won't answer my calls!
وهذا الوغد تشو بان يول لن يجيب على مكالماتي!
Don't just stand there. Go get the car ready!
لا تقف هناك فقط. اذهب وجهز السيارة!
Forward, march!
إلى الأمام، المسيرة!
Right flank, march!
الجناح الأيمن، مسيرة!
He's going down the main staircase. Stop him.
إنه ينزل الدرج الرئيسي. أوقفوه.
I'm on my way up.
أنا في طريقي إلى الأعلى.
Damn it!
عليك اللعنة!
Wow.
رائع.
-Halt! -One, two!
-توقف! -واحد، اثنان!
That's all I know.
هذا كل ما أعرفه.
But Min Ju-yeong was the one who gave out the orders.
لكن مين جو يونغ هو الذي أصدر الأوامر.
So you get what I'm saying, right?
إذن أنت تفهم ما أقوله، أليس كذلك؟
There's a whole story behind this.
هناك قصة كاملة وراء هذا.
I'm serious.
أنا جادة.
-They're here. -What do you mean?
-إنهم هنا. -ماذا تقصد؟
Who's here? Cho Pan-yeol?
من هنا؟ تشو بان يول؟
Well, we got what we came for.
حسنًا، لقد حصلنا على ما أتينا من أجله.
-Let's wrap this up. -Wrap what up?
-دعونا ننهي هذا الأمر. -ننهي ماذا؟
Jeez, what's the matter with you guys?
يا إلهي، ما الأمر معكم يا رفاق؟
Come on!
تعال!
No, don't do this!
لا، لا تفعل هذا!
Hey, call 112! Call the police!
مرحباً، اتصل بالرقم ١١٢! اتصل بالشرطة!
No, I meant 119! The emergency response team!
لا، أقصد ١١٩! فريق الاستجابة للطوارئ!
119, my ass.
119، مؤخرتي.
Does the commissioner know what you're doing?
هل المفوض يعرف ما تفعله؟
Where's Cho Pan-yeol? Bring him here!
أين تشو بان يول؟ أحضروه إلى هنا!
I already told you everything I know!
لقد أخبرتك بكل ما أعرفه!
I don't know Min Ju-yeong that well!
أنا لا أعرف مين جو يونغ جيدًا!
Save your excuses for the reporters.
احتفظ بأعذارك للمراسلين.
No, please stop!
لا، من فضلك توقف!
Don't do this!
لا تفعل هذا!
Come on, let's talk it out.
هيا، دعنا نتحدث عن الأمر.
The two of us can leave quietly.
يمكننا أن نغادر بهدوء.
Goodbye.
مع السلامة.
HAPPY INSUNG WITH CITIZENS
غناء سعيد مع المواطنين
Get away from me!
ابتعد عني!
Why are you doing this to me?
لماذا تفعل بي هذا؟
Jeez, you scared me!
يا إلهي، لقد أخفتني!
He says he's not the mayor.
يقول أنه ليس رئيس البلدية.
If he's not the mayor, then who is?
إذا لم يكن هو رئيس البلدية فمن هو إذن؟
Look at him spinning.
أنظر إليه وهو يدور.
He must be dizzy.
لابد أنه يشعر بالدوار.
Authorities have confirmed Min,
وأكدت السلطات أن مين،
a former customs officer involved in a recent drug smuggling case,
ضابط جمارك سابق متورط في قضية تهريب مخدرات حديثة،
had long been colluding with Mayor Roh Deok-gyu
كان متواطئًا منذ فترة طويلة مع رئيس البلدية روه ديوك جيو
and other high-ranking officials,
وغيرهم من كبار المسؤولين،
causing widespread shock.
تسبب في صدمة واسعة النطاق.
Man, what a relief.
يا رجل، ما هذا الإرتياح.
Shall we eat now?
هل نأكل الآن؟
My appetite is back.
شهيتي عادت.
I'll go get some water.
سأذهب لأحضر بعض الماء.
Yoon Dong-ju.
يون دونغ جو.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Yeah, you don't look so well.
نعم، أنت لا تبدو بخير.
Did you overdo it? You look drained.
هل بالغت في ذلك؟ تبدو منهكًا.
Who, me? Of course not.
من أنا؟ بالطبع لا.
The meat is so tender and good.
اللحوم طرية ولذيذة للغاية.
-Ma'am, can we get more meat? -Okay.
-سيدتي، هل يمكننا الحصول على المزيد من اللحوم؟ -حسنًا.
-And more kimchi, please.
-والمزيد من الكيمتشي، من فضلك. -حسنا.
-Hey. -Oh.
-هي. -أوه.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Eat up.
تناول الطعام.
Where are Dong-ju and Jong-hyeon?
أين دونغ جو وجونغ هيون؟
They went to the restroom.
لقد ذهبوا إلى الحمام.
Are you stupid?
هل انت غبي؟
Don't push yourself. It'll be more obvious if you do.
لا تُرهق نفسك، فالأمر سيكون أوضح إن فعلت.
I'm just dizzy because of my meds.
أنا فقط أشعر بالدوار بسبب أدويتي.
I think that doctor's a quack.
أعتقد أن هذا الطبيب دجال.
Button up before Han-na sees you.
أغلق الأزرار قبل أن تراك هانا.
What?
ماذا؟
What are you staring at?
ماذا تحدق فيه؟
I guess I meant a lot to you.
أعتقد أنني أعني الكثير بالنسبة لك.
Stop talking nonsense.
توقف عن الكلام الهراء.
The captain filled me in.
لقد أطلعني القبطان على الأمر.
You should be grateful to Sergeant Kim for the rest of your life.
ينبغي عليك أن تكون ممتنًا للرقيب كيم لبقية حياتك.
I can't believe he sacrificed all that for a mess like you.
لا أستطيع أن أصدق أنه ضحى بكل هذا من أجل شخص مثلك.
What are you talking about?
ماذا تتحدث عنه؟
Sergeant Kim went so far
لقد ذهب الرقيب كيم إلى هذا الحد
as to give up all his shares to save you.
كأنه يتنازل عن جميع أسهمه لإنقاذك.
Help us.
ساعدنا.
I mean, I get it.
أعني أنني أفهم ذلك.
I'm definitely charming enough
أنا بالتأكيد ساحر بما فيه الكفاية
to be worth your whole fortune.
أن تكون قيمتها تساوي ثروتك بأكملها.
Yoon Dong-ju.
يون دونغ جو.
Your meds are causing some serious side effects.
أدويتك تسبب بعض الآثار الجانبية الخطيرة.
Answer it. It's the nursing home.
أجب عليه. إنه دار التمريض.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
It's my fault that you got hurt.
إنه خطئي أنك تعرضت للأذى.
I'm so sorry.
أنا آسف جدا.
Don't say that.
لا تقل ذلك.
You have nothing to be sorry about.
ليس لديك ما تأسف عليه.
I heard the whole story.
سمعت القصة كاملة.
Thank you, Dong-ju.
شكرا لك، دونغ جو.
What happened
ماذا حدث
to your face?
إلى وجهك؟
It's making me upset.
إنه يجعلني منزعجًا.
You're like a son to me.
أنت مثل ابني.
I shouldn't have been so harsh on you.
لا ينبغي لي أن أكون قاسياً معك بهذه الطريقة.
You must've been upset when I said we shouldn't see each other.
لا بد أنك كنت مستاءً عندما قلت أننا لا ينبغي أن نرى بعضنا البعض.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
Dong-ju.
دونغ جو.
Yes?
نعم؟
From now on…
من الآن فصاعدا…
let's live as mother and son.
دعونا نعيش كأم وابنها.
Let's stay close
دعونا نبقى قريبين
and be there for each other, okay?
وكونوا هناك من أجل بعضكم البعض، حسنًا؟
My dear Dong-ju.
عزيزي دونغ جو.
My son.
ابني.
Don't cry.
لا تبكي.
I'm so sorry.
أنا آسف جدا.
The Japanese canceled the deal.
ألغى اليابانيون الصفقة.
They said penalty fees weren't necessary.
قالوا أن رسوم الجزاء ليست ضرورية.
That means they're going to kill me.
وهذا يعني أنهم سيقتلونني.
What should we do with the Candy?
ماذا يجب أن نفعل مع الحلوى؟
He got mixed up with Min Ju-yeong while taking bribes from businesses.
لقد اختلط مع مين جو يونغ أثناء تلقيه رشاوى من الشركات.
Turns out, he had gambling debts and even borrowed from loan sharks.
اتضح أنه كان عليه ديون القمار وحتى أنه اقترض من المرابين.
Sergeant Kim.
الرقيب كيم.
You found Oh Jong-gu?
هل وجدت أوه جونغ جو؟
Why are you getting in? Get out!
لماذا تدخل؟ اخرج!
Where do you think you're going?
إلى أين تعتقد أنك ذاهب؟
We have to catch Min Ju-yeong.
علينا أن نقبض على مين جو يونغ.
What are you doing? Let's move.
ماذا تفعل؟ دعنا نتحرك.
Goodness gracious.
رباه.
We need to find something here to figure out where Min Ju-yeong is.
نحن بحاجة إلى العثور على شيء هنا لمعرفة مكان مين جو يونغ.
I'm going to the scene for a bit.
سأذهب إلى مكان الحادث قليلاً.
Don't worry about things here.
لا تقلق بشأن الأشياء هنا.
MOM
أم
Detective Lee, let's keep digging.
المحقق لي، دعنا نستمر في الحفر.
Mom, I'm busy right now. I'll call you later.
أمي، أنا مشغول الآن. سأتصل بك لاحقًا.
What?
ماذا؟
Why are you looking for Dong-ju?
لماذا تبحث عن دونغ جو؟
I have to ask him something about his insurance policy,
أريد أن أسأله شيئًا عن بوليصة التأمين الخاصة به،
but he won't answer his phone.
ولكنه لا يجيب على هاتفه.
By the way, what's wrong with him? Is he sick?
بالمناسبة، ما به؟ هل هو مريض؟
You're not seeing him, are you?
أنت لا تراه، أليس كذلك؟
It's not a big deal.
إنها ليست مشكلة كبيرة.
And Mom,
وأمي
I'll handle my own business.
سأتعامل مع أعمالي بنفسي.
Stay out of it.
ابقى خارجا من ذلك.
SAFETY IS OUR COMPANY'S TOP PRIORITY
السلامة هي الأولوية القصوى لشركتنا
Did you catch him?
هل قبضت عليه؟
No, but I think he's still here. Let's split up and search for him.
لا، لكن أعتقد أنه لا يزال هنا. لنفترق ونبحث عنه.
Hey, what are you doing?
مهلا، ماذا تفعل؟
Don't do anything and stay put.
لا تفعل أي شيء وابق في مكانك.
What do you mean, Captain?
ماذا تقصد يا كابتن؟
-Let's go. -Uncuff me!
-دعنا نذهب. -حررني!
-Wait right here. -Hey, Jae-hong!
-انتظر هنا. -مرحبًا، جاي هونغ!
Kim Jong-hyeon! Captain!
كيم جونغ هيون! كابتن!
You can't leave me here like this!
لا يمكنك تركي هنا هكذا!
We need to go together!
نحن بحاجة للذهاب معا!
Damn it.
عليك اللعنة.
Oh Jong-gu!
أوه جونغ-جو!
He's not here.
إنه ليس هنا.
Sergeant Kim.
الرقيب كيم.
Dung-ju can't get those cuffs off, right?
دونج جو لا يستطيع إزالة تلك الأصفاد، أليس كذلك؟
I'm positive that he can't get them off.
أنا متأكد من أنه لا يستطيع التخلص منهم.
Hey, Oh Jong-gu!
مهلا، أوه جونغ-جو!
Damn it.
عليك اللعنة.
Where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
There's no way out now.
لا يوجد مخرج الآن .
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Looks like you need another beating.
يبدو أنك بحاجة إلى ضرب آخر.
Did you follow me because you want to die?
هل اتبعتني لأنك تريد الموت؟
No.
لا.
I'm here to catch you.
أنا هنا لأمسك بك.
Hey.
يا.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
This was pretty uncomfortable.
كان هذا غير مريح تماما.
Shall we start our rematch?
هل نبدأ مباراة العودة؟
Rematch?
مباراة العودة؟
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
You trying to use your head, asshole?
هل تحاول استخدام رأسك أيها الأحمق؟
Are you trying to tire me out?
هل تحاول أن تتعبني؟
Took you long enough to catch on.
لقد استغرق الأمر وقتًا طويلاً حتى تدرك ذلك.
Guess you're not totally empty in there.
أعتقد أنك لست فارغًا تمامًا هناك.
To be honest, you pack a pretty mean punch.
لكي أكون صادقا، لديك لكمة قاسية إلى حد ما.
Hey, focus.
مهلا، التركيز.
This is why you can't read your opponent's movements.
لهذا السبب لا يمكنك قراءة تحركات خصمك.
How dare you try to lecture me?
كيف تجرؤ على محاولة إلقاء محاضرة علي؟
Do I look like a joke to you?
هل أبدو لك كأنني مزحة؟
No.
لا.
You look pathetic.
تبدو مثيرا للشفقة.
What?
ماذا؟
I thought you were a cool athlete
اعتقدت أنك رياضي رائع
when you were in the ring.
عندما كنت في الحلبة.
You're the reason why I ended up like this, you little shit.
أنت السبب في أنني انتهيت هكذا، أيها الوغد الصغير.
If you hadn't backed out of that contract,
إذا لم تتراجع عن هذا العقد،
I wouldn't have become Min Ju-yeong's lapdog.
لن أكون كلبًا صغيرًا لمين جو يونغ.
Don't blame other people.
لا تلوم الآخرين.
Blame your stupidity.
ألقي اللوم على غبائك.
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
That's what you told me
هذا ما قلته لي
when I lost at the national team trials.
عندما خسرت في اختبارات المنتخب الوطني.
I didn't learn much from you,
لم أتعلم منك الكثير
but I do remember that much.
ولكنني أتذكر ذلك كثيرًا.
You arrogant little bastard.
أيها الوغد المتغطرس الصغير.
Damn it.
عليك اللعنة.
Go learn some more, asshole. This is how you use your head.
تعلّم أكثر يا أحمق. هكذا تستخدم عقلك.
Get up.
استيقظ.
Now that I think about it,
الآن بعد أن فكرت في الأمر،
there's one more thing I remember.
هناك شيء آخر أتذكره.
It's what you told me every time I stepped in the ring.
هذا ما قلته لي في كل مرة دخلت فيها الحلبة.
You said too much greed
لقد قلت الكثير من الجشع
weighs down your punches.
يثقل لكماتك.
And if that happens,
وإذا حدث ذلك،
you're finished!
لقد انتهيت!
Hey, Yoon Dong-ju! I told you to stay in the car!
يا يون دونغ جو! قلت لك ابق في السيارة!
What's this?
ما هذا؟
Hey, Yoon Dong-ju!
مهلا، يون دونغ جو!
This little mutt just won't stay tied up.
هذا الكلب الصغير لن يبقى مقيدًا.
Oh, come on. I got Oh Jong-gu.
أوه، هيا. لقد حصلت على أوه جونغ-جو.
Good for you, damn it!
جيد بالنسبة لك، اللعنة!
Oh Jong-gu, you're under arrest for violating the Narcotics Control Act
أوه جونغ-جو، أنت قيد الاعتقال بتهمة انتهاك قانون مكافحة المخدرات.
and for the illegal use and sale of license plates.
ولاستخدام وبيع لوحات السيارات بشكل غير قانوني.
Senior Officer Ji!
الضابط الكبير جي!
You also knew Dong-ju was unwell, didn't you?
لقد كنت تعلم أيضًا أن دونغ جو كان مريضًا، أليس كذلك؟
You knew?
هل عرفت؟
-Has he gotten worse? -Well, the thing is…
-هل أصبح حاله أسوأ؟ -حسنًا، المشكلة هي...
He went to the hospital with Sergeant Kim not long ago.
لقد ذهب إلى المستشفى مع الرقيب كيم منذ فترة ليست طويلة.
-You all know Dong-ju shouldn't be here. -But…
-أنتم جميعًا تعلمون أن دونغ جو لا ينبغي أن يكون هنا. -لكن...
Oh Jong-gu.
أوه جونغ-جو.
Does it hurt?
هل يؤلمك؟
It doesn't hurt at all.
لا يؤلم على الإطلاق.
See?
يرى؟
Oh Jong-gu has a really hard head.
أوه جونغ جو لديه رأس صعب حقًا.
See? It does hurt.
هل رأيت؟ إنه يؤلم.
This is nothing.
هذا لا شيء.
I'm okay. It's not a big deal.
أنا بخير. ليس الأمر مهمًا.
It might be a tiny hairline fracture,
ربما يكون كسرًا شعريًا صغيرًا،
-but as long as I take care of it-- -It is a big deal!
-ولكن طالما أنني أعتني به-- -إنه أمر كبير!
What's the matter?
ماذا جرى؟
How long are you going to pretend that you're fine in front of me?
إلى متى ستظل تتظاهر بأنك بخير أمامي؟
I told you to be honest if you were hurting.
لقد قلت لك أن تكون صادقا إذا كنت تتألم.
Just lean on me instead of struggling on your own!
فقط اعتمد عليّ بدلاً من النضال بمفردك!
You're not alone anymore.
أنت لم تعد وحيدا بعد الآن.
I don't want you to be in pain, so if you care about me…
لا أريدك أن تشعر بالألم، لذا إذا كنت تهتم بي...
How long have you known?
منذ متى وأنت تعرف؟
How could I not know?
كيف لا أعرف؟
I waited until you were ready to tell me.
انتظرت حتى أصبحت مستعدًا لإخباري.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
What are you sorry for?
لماذا أنت آسف؟
I'm the one who didn't tell you.
أنا الذي لم أخبرك.
I didn't want you to see me sick and worry,
لم أكن أريدك أن تراني مريضًا وأقلق،
so I kept it from you.
لذلك أخفيته عنك.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
What now?
ماذا الآن؟
Don't worry too much.
لا تقلق كثيرا.
You see,
هل ترى،
Kim Jong-hyeon
كيم جونغ هيون
introduced me to a good doctor.
قدمني إلى طبيب جيد.
She said I'll get better if I take my meds and get treated.
قالت إنني سأتحسن إذا تناولت أدويتي وتلقيت العلاج.
You'd better.
من الأفضل لك ذلك.
If you don't, I'll kill you myself.
إذا لم تفعل ذلك، سأقتلك بنفسي.
From now on, tell me if you feel even slightly off.
من الآن فصاعدا، أخبرني إذا كنت تشعر بأي شيء غير طبيعي حتى ولو قليلا.
Keep me posted on your hospital visits and meds.
أبقيني على اطلاع بشأن زياراتك للمستشفى وأدويتك.
Don't leave anything out, okay?
لا تترك أي شيء خارجًا، حسنًا؟
Okay.
تمام.
Actually, I just took my meds so I feel a bit dizzy.
في الواقع، لقد تناولت للتو أدويتي لذلك أشعر بالدوار قليلاً.
Are you feeling okay these days?
هل تشعر أنك بخير هذه الأيام؟
Yeah, I'm fine.
نعم، أنا بخير.
It's been a while since I took any meds.
لقد مر وقت طويل منذ أن تناولت أي أدوية.
I must be your medicine.
يجب أن أكون دوائك.
I guess so.
اعتقد ذلك.
I'm so glad.
انا سعيد جدا.
I'm sorry, Han-na.
أنا آسف، هانا.
Give me your hand.
أعطني يدك.
Does it hurt?
هل يؤلمك؟
No, it doesn't.
لا، لا يحدث ذلك.
-By the way… -Yeah?
-بالمناسبة... -نعم؟
Can we do this?
هل يمكننا أن نفعل هذا؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
We totally can.
نحن نستطيع ذلك تماما.
RESTRICTED NUMBER
رقم مقيد
Goddammit.
يا إلهي.
What about the goods?
ماذا عن البضاعة؟
This looks a bit different from what you showed me before.
يبدو هذا مختلفًا بعض الشيء عما أظهرته لي من قبل.
Is it fake?
هل هو مزيف؟
How much of this do you have?
كم لديك من هذا؟
A whole truckload.
شاحنة كاملة.
That's more than we can handle.
هذا أكثر مما يمكننا التعامل معه.
Money, you see.
المال، كما ترى.
It's free.
إنه مجاني.
But I need a favor in return.
ولكنني أحتاج إلى خدمة في المقابل.
"A hazy fog rolls in."
"يتدحرج الضباب الكثيف."
"The street flows along."
"الشارع يتدفق على طول."
"With no harbor to drop the anchor,
"بدون ميناء لإسقاط المرساة،
I stand with my hands on the red postbox on the street corner."
"أقف ويدي على صندوق البريد الأحمر في زاوية الشارع."
It's time for you to return my book.
لقد حان الوقت لإرجاع كتابي.
Min Ju-yeong.
مين جو يونغ.
The bastard is crazier than you can ever imagine.
هذا الوغد أكثر جنونًا مما يمكنك تخيله.
He's never satisfied unless he takes what he wants
إنه لا يرضى أبدًا إلا إذا أخذ ما يريد
or destroys what he can't have.
أو يدمر ما لا يستطيع الحصول عليه.
I can't say when he'll snap,
لا أستطيع أن أقول متى سينفجر،
but now could be it since he has nowhere to run.
لكن الآن قد يكون هذا هو الحال لأنه ليس لديه مكان يهرب إليه.
Be careful.
احرص.
179-45, CHEONGMA 7 FACTORY, CHEONGMA-DONG, YUWOL-GU
179-45، مصنع تشونغما 7، تشونغما-دونغ، يوول-غو
CAPTAIN GO MAN-SIK
الكابتن جو مان سيك
Yes, Captain?
نعم يا كابتن؟
We got word that the truck carrying drugs is heading toward Cheongma-dong.
وصلتنا رسالة مفادها أن الشاحنة التي تحمل المخدرات متجهة نحو تشيونغما دونغ.
Jae-hong and I are on our way.
أنا وجاي هونغ في طريقنا.
I'll join up with Jong-hyeon and go.
سأنضم إلى جونغ هيون ونذهب.
Officer Yoon!
الضابط يون!
Officer Yoon, I'm here!
الضابط يون، أنا هنا!
Car keys!
مفاتيح السيارة!
Take her.
خذها.
Han-na, are you on your way?
هانا، هل أنت في طريقك؟
The truck might explode.
قد تنفجر الشاحنة.
We have to stop it on the road before it reaches Cheongma-dong.
علينا أن نوقفه على الطريق قبل أن يصل إلى تشونغما دونغ.
-Okay. -Got it.
-حسنًا. -فهمت.
Everyone, be careful.
الجميع، كونوا حذرين.
Is it that truck?
هل هذه هي الشاحنة؟
It's the truck!
إنها الشاحنة!
Is that Jong-hyeon?
هل هذا جونغ هيون؟
Keep your cool.
حافظ على هدوئك.
Hold on tight.
تمسك جيدا.
Get out.
اخرج.
Get out now.
اخرج الآن.
Damn it!
عليك اللعنة!
-Get the hell out! -Screw you, you bastards!
-اخرج من هنا! - اذهب إلى الجحيم أيها الأوغاد!
Don't come near here!
لا تقترب من هنا!
You can look forward to it.
يمكنك أن تتطلع إلى ذلك.
Today is going to be a very memorable day.
اليوم سيكون يومًا لا يُنسى.
What's Min Ju-yeong's next plan?
ما هي خطة مين جو يونغ القادمة؟
Choose your words wisely.
إختر كلماتك بحكمة.
Who would help Min Ju-yeong?
من سيساعد مين جو يونغ؟
It's time. Keep an eye out.
لقد حان الوقت. انتبه.
Listen carefully to what I'm about to say.
استمع بعناية إلى ما سأقوله.
Dozens of high-ranking officials in Insung
عشرات من كبار المسؤولين في إنسونغ
have long been in cahoots with Min Ju-yeong.
لقد كانوا متواطئين لفترة طويلة مع مين جو يونغ.
Do you think you can tackle it overnight?
هل تعتقد أنك قادر على معالجة الأمر بين عشية وضحاها؟
I'll give you a chance.
سأعطيك فرصة.
We have to find him fast
علينا أن نجده بسرعة
before the bastard throws another curveball.
قبل أن يلقي الوغد كرة منحنية أخرى.
When everyone burned with passion…
عندما كان الجميع يحترقون بالعاطفة...
Move!
يتحرك!
A scumbag like you doesn't get to make excuses.
شخص حقير مثلك لا يحق له تقديم الأعذار.
Don't think it's all over just because I'm gone.
لا تظن أن الأمر قد انتهى فقط لأنني رحلت.
We were heroes.
لقد كنا أبطالاً.
Subtitle: Jenny Kim
الترجمة الفرعية: جيني كيم